There is a let's jump on to another one of a powerful tool but I will not suggest you
to use it against an environment so until and unless you turn off the different mechanism
completely because it will be easily creating a detection and it will be blocking the tool
okay this sharpened and the blood from both tools are really really powerful to enumerate
all the domain-based information so which I have seen plenty of tools that can angry
it can advance if it cannot scan the network infrastructure in the environment but if you see
this tool it will be mainly focusing on the domain and user-based information let's take an
example who is an RDP users and how to like how to move to that user host so which user has
the which privileges and so it will it will be basically it will be showing the information which
will be easy to get a privileged escalation and which will be easy to get information about the
users to move to a lateral moment and to understand which users have the administrator and which
user has how much privileges he has okay so in overall understanding the tool will be collecting
the users and domain-based information and helping us to find out a best and best path to move
forward to choose which account we can use to move laterally and which account we can use for
a privilege escalation okay so this tool is also used for a privilege escalation to find out which
which account we can use for further for ex-escalating privileges okay so let's go to the
sharpen community edition you can find the sharpen community edition here and you can see few
of the commands that needs to get in but if you are a Kali Linux user so no don't worry about that
you will be you can easily get the sharpen done but can't okay you can sharpen it so here you can
find in the user shared sharpen folder there is few executable was hiding inside the folder
so let's sum again it's to the c user
sharpen to sharpen and here you can find the sharpen.exe executable
so I just move I just download this executable in my Windows
destination okay so I never did anything I didn't download it from anywhere I just used a
Kali machine and downloaded the sharpen here okay so I think my machine has stuck let me I need
to restart this let's restart and we'll discuss
so maybe you have here about a few questions in the interview what's about the sharpen done
that one so sharpen is basically a data collector it will collect the information from the device
even in the in the Windows device or if you run the sharpen against the server or active directory
it will collect as much information and it will just collect the information okay it will not
show you anything just collect information it's a collector tool okay so data collector for
a blood hunt it collect the information to be to showcase to be the information you need a you
need a blood hunt okay the similar tool blood hunt okay the executing blood hunt is also
is available in the Kali Linux so not a problem we can you can easily get a blood hunt tool
in Kali Linux 2 so just execute a blood hunt it will be running in the server one two seven
dot zero dot zero dot one and 80 it will automatically open and it will it will you can you can login
again and so let's uh let's see our Windows machine get turned on
let's wait for a sec and uh and we'll get our Windows machine up and I'll show you something
yeah our Windows machine get uh powered up let's open
let me check if I have a sharp hunt yeah here here here we have a short context executable
here let me go for uh pmd and send us an administrator
okay so here we have a sharpened and uh this is the command you can uh you can execute
to get an information so basically the sharpened will be collecting the information in uh
see as you file so you can execute this command uh uh in a you can execute this command and
like to collect the information okay it's a collection method so it will collect basically all
the information like session so who is an RDB users and what privileges he have and uh everything
everything from the domain okay uh so currently our uh test syndrome and do not have a uh sorry
our test syndrome and do not have a uh active directory and domain domain uh the
active directory does not configure so we will not get any kind of information so let me execute
the command anyway okay uh and it was showing some kind of selection method is unknown
so we have an all to collect uh these information like collection with a group local group
advanced RDB ED comments etc uh but let's let's see this
execute mostly this
so uh I just executed this command and uh sorry my videos get uh uh passed I don't know why
uh maybe uh it was considered a lot of memory uh the video get break up uh so it showed an error
unable to get the domain information so you can see here uh but uh I just uh I just uh I just
needs to show an example to you uh how this blood control will uh work okay so let me uh I just
selected a few of the uh things before and this is the blood hunt uh sick data and uh I will be
opening uh this one uploading this one to the tool and uh you can see it has been successfully
uploaded uh let me go towards the uh towards this and I can see uh there is a lot of information
since it has been uh collected and uh here you can find the the map north uh seven uh kingdom
here you can find all the domains and computer one GPU groups uh 12 etc etc so here you can
find a search command you can use a search command to uh search the uh users here you can find
authenticated user distributed users uh remote desktop user let me go for a remote desktop user
and uh click on this so here you can see two section was there and uh
oh it was connecting to stark and uh this is uh mind domain main user
so inside you have fun user and these are or the uh users which have a RDP uh based connection
so so this is how we will be showing all each and every information so to you how to how to
which account we can use and how to we can enumerate the uh privileges and all okay
so it will show you as much of information so what informations you know when the account was
created uh when it was possible going to expand a city of the account uh everything everything basically
okay uh so this tool will be really helpful to enumerate and focus the information uh so what uh
uh what you need and uh not only that you can see who are all the uh authenticated users
to be good domain users you can see the domain users in the domain who are all the domain users
okay uh so there is uh 15 members who has a domain uh based uh domain uh domain users and
here you can see the user name actually are so here you can uh find all the information you know
what account we can choose to uh uh choose to elevate the privileges or um that really from
on machine to another okay i think uh we are good with this and uh we'll hop off uh from here and
we'll connect you guys in the next video see you bye bye